{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "It's my birthday this Friday. Welcome to my party at night. \"Thank you. ___. Happy Birthday to You.\"",
      "a": "I will",
      "b": "I do",
      "c": "I have",
      "d": "I can",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Will\" is used to show that someone is willing or ready to do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I thought Pauline ___ like something to read, so I have brought her two books.",
      "a": "might",
      "b": "may",
      "c": "must",
      "d": "can",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Can: used to say that something is possible",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Paul ___ be in Phuket. I saw him in town only six hours ago.",
      "a": "shouldn't",
      "b": "mustn't",
      "c": "may not",
      "d": "can't",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Might: if something might happen or might be true, there is a possibility that it may happen or may be true, but you are not at all certain ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I wonder how Daniel _________ that to the director.",
      "a": "dare saying",
      "b": "dared to say",
      "c": "dared say",
      "d": "not dare say",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Dare: To be brave enough to do something that is risky or that you are afraid to do ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Must Claire and I do it now? \"No, you ___.\"",
      "a": "needn't",
      "b": "won't",
      "c": "don't",
      "d": "can't",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Need: used in negative sentences when saying that something is not necessary or not always true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This office ought _________ by tomorrow.",
      "a": "to be cleaned",
      "b": "to clean",
      "c": "be cleaned",
      "d": "clean",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Passive voice: Ought + to be + PP",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Could we call you by your nickname? \"Yes, you ___.\"",
      "a": "could",
      "b": "will",
      "c": "was able to",
      "d": "may",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- May: used to say that someone is allowed to do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Could you lend me a pen? \"Yes, _________\"",
      "a": "could",
      "b": "might",
      "c": "may",
      "d": "can",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Can: to be allowed to do something or to have the right or power to do something \n- Could - can",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "From what I hear about their trip, their hotel and the weather, they ___ their holidays very much.",
      "a": "shouldn't have enjoyed",
      "b": "would have enjoyed",
      "c": "couldn't have enjoyed",
      "d": "needn't have enjoyed",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Could have PP: used to say that something was a possibility in the past, but did not actually happen",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jason ___ terribly tired last night. He had been working without a rest for over twelve hours.",
      "a": "had been",
      "b": "may be",
      "c": "must have been",
      "d": "used to be",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Must:  used to say you think something is very likely to be true or very likely to have happened",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}